I realize that you've always been an outcast
我发现你总是不受欢迎
It's not everyone at school who likes to think
不是每个人都天赋异禀
To find a student that's like you,
像你的学生难找出
I've had one or maybe two,
也许一两个相符
but the good ones disappear before I blink
但转眼之间就消失无影
Now, I understand you have your reservations
现在我理解你感觉这样不妥
It's hard to have a brain as large as yours
没人知道、了解得比你多
But if we don't win these games,
但要是我们败北
well, I think I've made it plain,
比赛并非无所谓
what will happen if we have the losing scores!
如果失分将会有什么风波!
Unleash the magic, unleash the magic
释放这魔力，释放这魔力
If we lose, then you're to blame
我们输，你也要受罪
They all have used it, maybe abused it,
他们用魔力，随便来作弊
so then why can't we do the same?
我们不用就会血亏
Call it power, call it magic,
叫它力量，叫它魔力
if we lose, it will be tragic
如果输，就会是悲剧
More important is the knowledge we'll have lost!
更重要的是知识将会错过!
A chance like this won't come again,
这种机会很难再临
You'll regret not giving in
你会后悔没有听
Isn't understanding magic worth the cost?
难道"理解魔法"说服力不多?
Unleash the magic, unleash the magic
释放这魔力，释放这魔力
We're not friends here after all
对手非我们同伙
Our only interest in this business
我们只是想，在比赛里
is seeing Canterlot High School fall
看着坎高失败坠落
What I'm suggesting's very simple,
我所要求的并不过火
and since it's win-win on all scores
而且双赢这很稳妥
You only want to learn about the
你想从捕获的魔力中
magic that you have stored
学习一切成果
And as for me and all the others,
不要对我和同学吝啬
we only want what we deserve
我们只想取回应得
That our school will clinch the win,
我们学校将胜利
And my legacy will endure!
我名声将更显赫!
Unleash the magic, unleash the magic
释放这魔力，释放这魔力
If we lose, then it's a crime
我们输，多么埋汰
But we can win it if you begin it,
我们能胜利，只要用魔力
it's up to you to not fail this time
看你对此想如何表态
Unleash the magic, free the magic now
Imagine all I'll learn by setting it free
想象有多少知识能学习
Unleash the magic, free the magic now
And now winning these games depends on me
同学的胜利全靠我自己
Unleash the magic, free the magic now
And what doors might open if I try to use it
未知的门后藏着多少秘密
Unleash the magic, free the magic now
Unleash the magic, free the magic
But the magic's what I really want to see
其中的魔力正和我的心意
Unleash the magic, free the magic
释放这魔力，使用这法宝